<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cloud Infrastructure on MuShop</title>
    <link>/cloud/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cloud Infrastructure on MuShop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 13:33:46 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/cloud/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prerequisites</title>
      <link>/cloud/prerequisites/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 14:51:01 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cloud/prerequisites/</guid>
      <description>In order connect the MuShop application with services in Oracle Cloud Infrastructure, several configurations are necessary. These tenancy configurations will be used to properly provision and/or connect cloud services: Create a file with the following information to simplify lookups later:
region:# Region where resources will be provisioned (ex us-phoenix-1)tenancy:# Tenancy OCID valueuser:# API User OCID valuecompartment:# Compartment OCID valuekey:# Private API Key file path (ex /Users/jdoe/.oci/oci_key.pem)fingerprint:# Public API Key fingerprint (ex 43:65:2c.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup</title>
      <link>/cloud/setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 15:49:36 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cloud/setup/</guid>
      <description>MuShop provides an umbrella helm chart called setup, which includes several recommended installations on the cluster. These represent common 3rd party services, which integrate with Oracle Cloud Infrastructure or enable certain application features.
   Chart Purpose Option Default     Prometheus Service metrics aggregation prometheus.enabled true   Grafana Infrastructure/service visualization dashboards grafana.enabled true   Metrics Server Support for Horizontal Pod Autoscaling metrics-server.enabled true   Ingress Nginx Ingress controller and public Load Balancer ingress-nginx.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deployment</title>
      <link>/cloud/deployment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 13:32:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cloud/deployment/</guid>
      <description>Provisioning Deploying the full application requires cloud backing services from Oracle Cloud Infrastructure. Provisioning these services may be done manually of course, but can also be done automatically through the use of OCI Service Broker. You are encouraged to explore each approach.
In all cases, begin by adding tenancy credentials to manage and connect services from within the cluster. Create a secret containing these values:
kubectl create secret generic oci-credentials \  --namespace mushop \  --from-literal=tenancy=&amp;lt;TENANCY_OCID&amp;gt; \  --from-literal=user=&amp;lt;USER_OCID&amp;gt; \  --from-literal=region=&amp;lt;USER_OCI_REGION&amp;gt; \  --from-literal=fingerprint=&amp;lt;PUBLIC_API_KEY_FINGERPRINT&amp;gt; \  --from-literal=passphrase=&amp;lt;PRIVATE_API_KEY_PASSPHRASE&amp;gt; \  --from-file=privatekey=&amp;lt;PATH_OF_PRIVATE_API_KEY&amp;gt;  NOTE: The passphrase entry is required.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
