<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>OCI Observability on MuShop</title>
    <link>https://oracle-quickstart.github.io/oci-cloudnative/tags/oci-observability/</link>
    <description>Recent content in OCI Observability on MuShop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://oracle-quickstart.github.io/oci-cloudnative/tags/oci-observability/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>OCI Monitoring</title>
      <link>https://oracle-quickstart.github.io/oci-cloudnative/observability/oci-monitoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle-quickstart.github.io/oci-cloudnative/observability/oci-monitoring/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The Oracle Cloud Infrastructure Monitoring service enables active and passive monitoring of cloud resources using the Metrics and Alarms features. Read more details here
This section focuses on monitoring system metrics of OKE (Oracle Cloud Infrastructure Container Engine for Kubernetes).
Pre-Requisites Deploy MuShop
OKE Cluster Metrics Navigate to Developer Services -&amp;gt; Kubernetes Clusters -&amp;gt; &amp;lt;Your_Cluster_Name&amp;gt;
Under Resources -&amp;gt; Metrics observe the following metrics
 Unschedulable pods, which can be used to trigger node pool scale operations when there are insufficient resources on which to schedule pods API Server requests per second, which is helpful to understand any underlying performance issues seen in the Kubernetes API server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OCI Health Checks</title>
      <link>https://oracle-quickstart.github.io/oci-cloudnative/observability/oci-healthcheck/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle-quickstart.github.io/oci-cloudnative/observability/oci-healthcheck/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Monitors the health of IP addresses and hostnames, as measured from geographic vantage points of your choosing, using HTTP and ping probes. After configuring a health check, you can view the monitor&amp;rsquo;s results. The results include the location from which the host was monitored, the availability of the endpoint, and the date and time the test was performed.
Pre-Requisites Deploy MuShop
Create Oracle Cloud Infrastructure Health Checks Navigate to Monitoring -&amp;gt; HealthChecks -&amp;gt; Create HealthChecks</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>