<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Setup on MuShop</title>
    <link>/tags/setup/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Setup on MuShop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 15:49:36 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/setup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Setup</title>
      <link>/cloud/setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 15:49:36 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cloud/setup/</guid>
      <description>MuShop provides an umbrella helm chart called setup, which includes several recommended installations on the cluster. These represent common 3rd party services, which integrate with Oracle Cloud Infrastructure or enable certain application features.
   Chart Purpose Option Default     Prometheus Service metrics aggregation prometheus.enabled true   Grafana Infrastructure/service visualization dashboards grafana.enabled true   Metrics Server Support for Horizontal Pod Autoscaling metrics-server.enabled true   Ingress Nginx Ingress controller and public Load Balancer ingress-nginx.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes Deployment</title>
      <link>/quickstart/kubernetes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 12:27:43 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/quickstart/kubernetes/</guid>
      <description>This deployment option utilizes helm for configuration and installation onto a Kubernetes cluster. It is recommended to use an Oracle Container Engine for Kubernetes cluster, however other standard Kubernetes clusters will also work.
cd deploy/complete/helm-chart dir deploy/complete/helm-chart  Path for Cloud Native deployment configurations using helm
 Deploying the complete MuShop application with backing services from Oracle Cloud Infrastructure involves the use of the following helm charts:
 setup: Installs umbrella chart dependencies on the cluster (optional) provision: Provisions OCI resources integrated with Service Broker (optional) mushop: Deploys the MuShop application runtime  To get started, create a namespace for the application and its associative deployments:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
